A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Civic Interests, Series D FA313
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Westchester County Organizations
  - Westchester County Organizations - Westchester Citizens' Housing Council, Inc., 1957-1961 (Box 53, Folder 0397A)
    David Rockefeller's contributions. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
  - Westchester County Organizations - Elmsford-Beacon Expressway, 1957-1961 (Box 53, Folder 398)
    Possible locations for expressway. Plan to have route through Estate. Map. No results. Report on projection of Traffic Flow Patterns in the Area, affected by Hawthorne Circle Improvement, Westchester County, New York. Correspondents include Warren T. Lindquist, John E. Lockwood, J. B. McCorran, W. Yates, Mrs. T. M. Waller, Hugh R. Pomeroy.
    76.7
  - Westchester County Organizations - Elmsford-Beacon Expressway, 1957-1961 (Box 53, Folder 0398A)
  - Westchester County Organizations - Elmsford-Beacon Expressway - Hawthorne Circle, 1958-1959 (Box 53, Folder 399)
    "Report on Projection of Traffic Flow Patterns in the Area Affected by the Hawthorne Circle Improvement; Westchester County, New York" by Shumavon & Buckley, consulting engineers. Correspondents include J. B. McCorran, W. Yates, Hugh R. Pomeroy.
  - Westchester County Organizations - Elmsford-Beacon Expressway - Hawthorne Circle, 1958-1959 (Box 53, Folder 0399A)
    David Rockefeller gift for survey was $22,500.